I'm Peppa Pig. [snorts]
-This is my little brother, George.
-[snorts]
-This is Mommy Pig.
-[Mommy Pig snorts]
And this is Daddy Pig.
-[Daddy Pig snorts]
-[all laugh]
Peppa Pig. [snorts]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a lovely sunny morning.
[snorts] Ah.
What a nice day for doing nothing.
[narrator] Daddy Pig loves doing nothing.
[snorts] Daddy, aren't you going
to work today?
No, Peppa, it's Saturday.
[narrator] Daddy Pig doesn't work
on Saturdays.
[snorts] Daddy Pig,
you'll be late for work.
But it's Saturday, Mommy Pig.
-Isn't it?
-No, it's Thursday.
[Daddy Pig yells]
[narrator] Daddy Pig works on Thursdays.
See you later.
[Peppa & George] Bye-bye.
[snorts] Poor Daddy, having to work.
Lucky Mommy,
you can play at home all day.
I'm not playing.
I'm working on my computer.
[George snorts]
[narrator] George wants to play
the Happy Mrs. Chicken game.
George, we can play
the Happy Mrs. Chicken game
after I've finished my work.
-Oh.
-[horn honks]
[narrator] Mommy Sheep and Suzy have come
to pick up Peppa for playgroup.
[bleats] Hello, Peppa.
[snorts] Hello, Suzy.
[Peppa & Suzy giggle]
Have a good day at playgroup.
Bye-bye, Mommy. Work hard.
Mrs. Sheep, do you work or do you play?
I'm going to be working very hard today.
[bleats] I'm off to the gym.
What do you do at the gym?
Running, jumping and skipping.
Mommy, that's not work. That's play.
[all laughing]
[narrator] Peppa and Suzy have arrived
at the playgroup.
[Peppa & Suzy] Hello, everyone.
[students] Hello, Peppa. Hello, Suzy.
[students giggling]
Ah-ho. Children, today we will play shops.
[all] Ooh.
Who wants to be shopkeeper?
[students] Me, me, me!
Peppa and Suzy can be shopkeepers.
Everyone else can be customers.
[narrator] Peppa and Suzy are going to run
a pretend shop.
What do we have to do?
I will take the money, Suzy,
and you can stack the shelves.
Okay.
[narrator] Danny Dog
is the first customer.
Hello, shopkeeper.
Hello, Mr. Dog.
Can I have some biscuits, please?
Suzy, have we got any biscuits?
No, but we've got a toy telephone.
How much will that be?
That will be a hundred pounds, please.
[giggles] Thank you.
Next, please.
[neighs] Hello, shopkeeper.
Can I have a loaf of bread, please?
No, but you can have a toy house.
Would you like it in a bag, sir?
Yes, please.
That will be one penny, please.
Oh, I haven't got enough money.
You can pay us next time you come in.
Gosh, this is hard work.
Yes.
[squeaks] Hello, shopkeeper.
What can I buy
for a million thousand pounds, please?
Suzy, what have we got
for a million thousand pounds?
Hmm.
A carrot?
Yes, please.
[narrator] Rebecca Rabbit likes carrots.
[all giggle]
[ringing]
-[narrator] It is home time.
-[students giggling]
[narrator] Daddy Pig has come
to collect Peppa and Suzy.
[horn honks]
Daddy, have you had a busy day?
Yes.
I've been working very hard.
We've been working very hard, too.
We've been shopkeepers.
Blah, blah, blah, the end.
And print.
[narrator] Mommy Pig
has finished her work.
[George giggles, then snorts]
Okay, George, perhaps we can just play
one game of Happy Mrs. Chicken.
We've earned it.
[squawks, then farting]
[George giggling]
Naughty, Mommy.
You're playing Happy Mrs. Chicken.
Oh, that's because George and I
have finished our work.
-Haven't we, George?
-[snorts]
We've all finished our work,
so, let's all play.
[chickens farting]
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and her family are going
for a drive to the mountains.
[snorts] Are we nearly there yet?
[snorts] Not yet, Peppa.
[both sigh]
Let's play a game.
We each have to spot a car
of our favorite color.
[Peppa & George] Yes!
My favorite color is green.
Mine is orange.
[snorts] Mine is red.
George, what's your favorite color?
Boo.
[narrator] George's favorite color
is blue.
[snorts] Let's see which color car
comes along first.
[children & Mommy Pig] Okay.
[horn honks]
[narrator] Here is Candy Cat
in her green car.
[chuckles] Green.
That's my favorite color.
I win.
[snorts] Hello, Candy.
[meows] Hello, Peppa.
[horn honks]
[narrator] Here is Danny Dog
in Granddad Dog's breakdown truck.
[snorts] Orange. So, I win.
Hello, Danny.
[woofs] Hello, Peppa.
[laughs] Here's another car.
-[horn honks]
-[Peppa] It's Suzy. Hello.
[bleats] Hello, Peppa.
-[snorts] Boo.
-Yes, George.
It's a blue car, so, you win.
[giggles]
[sighs] This is a silly game.
There isn't a red car anywhere.
There is one red car, Peppa.
Where?
[Daddy Pig laughs]
What color is our car?
Uh... it's red.
I win! I win!
[all laughing]
[narrator] The family have arrived
at the mountains.
We'll have a fantastic view
when we get to the top.
We're here.
[all] Hooray!
Look at the lovely sunny view.
[all yell]
[narrator] Oh, dear.
It has started to rain.
Where's the lovely view?
Uh... there's a lovely view.
[narrator] It is Miss Rabbit's
ice-cream stall.
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
Hello, Daddy Pig.
Four ice creams, please.
What flavors would you like?
Mint, orange, strawberry
and blueberry, please.
Okay.
[chuckles]
Look what I've got.
-Ice cream!
-[George snorts]
Oh. [chuckles]
They're our favorite colors.
That's right. [snorts]
Green for me.
Orange for me.
Strawberry red for me.
And George's is...
Boo.
[George giggles]
Yum, yum, yum.
-Yummy.
-Look.
The sun has come out.
[Daddy Pig] And look what else
has come out.
[George & Peppa] A rainbow!
[narrator] Peppa and George love rainbows.
[Daddy Pig] A rainbow only comes out
when it's rainy and sunny
at the same time.
[both] Ooh.
It's got all our favorite colors in it.
[Peppa] Yes. [snorts]
Red and orange and green and blue.
[both giggling]
And do you know what you find
at the end of a rainbow?
[both] No.
You find treasure.
Oh! Can we go and find the treasure now?
Okay.
The end of the rainbow looks like
it's just on the next hill.
Let's go.
[all] Whee!
[Daddy Pig & Peppa giggle]
♪ It's a rainy sunny day ♪
The rainbow's here to play ♪
♪ Rainbow, rainbow ♪
♪ Red and orange and yellow and green
And purple and blue ♪
♪ Rainbow, rainbow ♪
♪ It's a rainy sunny day ♪
[Peppa & George giggle]
Here we are.
Oh. Where's our rainbow gone?
It's moved to the next hill.
You cheeky rainbow.
Quick, let's catch it.
♪ Rainbow, rainbow ♪
♪ It's a rainy sunny day ♪
It's stopped raining.
And the rainbow is gone.
-[George crying]
-[Mommy Pig] Don't worry, George.
Maybe the rainbow has left
some treasure behind.
There's something over here.
Have you found the rainbow's treasure?
Yes, I have.
A big, muddy puddle.
[all] Hooray!
[all laughing]
This is the best rainbow treasure ever.
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a school day.
Peppa and her friends
are having a music lesson.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Miss Polly had a dolly ♪
[Pedro coughing]
Sorry, Madame Gazelle. [coughs]
[narrator] Oh, dear. Pedro has a cough.
Not to worry.
I'll ring Dr. Brown Bear.
[dialing]
[ringing]
Dr. Brown Bear speaking.
Hello, doctor, this is Madame Gazelle.
A child is ill.
Don't panic.
I'll come straightaway.
[siren wailing]
[Dr. Brown Bear panting]
-What seems to be the problem?
-I've got a cough. [coughs]
I see.
Is it a tickly cough or a chesty cough?
Um... I don't know.
But it goes like this:
-[Pedro coughs]
-Hmm.
And when did you get this cough?
When Madame Gazelle started singing.
It's nothing serious,
but Pedro's cough may be catching.
What do you mean, "catching"?
When one person has a cough,
sometimes, other people
get that cough, too.
Do I need medicine?
Just a little spoonful.
I'm afraid it doesn't taste very nice.
Ugh!
It tastes like an old shoe full of jam.
Thank you, Dr. Brown Bear.
-Goodbye.
-[students] Bye.
[both cough]
As I thought.
Pedro's cough is catching.
[narrator] Danny Dog and Suzy Sheep
have caught Pedro's cough.
[Suzy & Danny cough]
Open wide.
Ew!
It tastes of carpet-flavored yogurt.
Ugh!
It tastes of flowers.
Well done for taking your medicine
so well.
Do you ever get ill, Dr. Brown Bear?
No, Peppa, I'm never ill.
I eat an apple a day.
-Goodbye.
-[students] Bye.
[ringing]
[narrator] It is home time.
The children's parents are here
to pick them up.
Mommy, Daddy, I've got a cough. [coughs]
Dr. Brown Bear came
and looked after us.
He gave us horrible medicine.
Madame Gazelle, can you sing
your song now?
Of course, Peppa.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Miss Polly had a dolly who was ♪
[coughs]
[all coughing]
[narrator] Oh, dear. All the grown-ups
have caught Pedro's cough.
[rings]
Dr. Brown Bear speaking.
This is Peppa Pig. [snorts]
All the grown-ups are ill.
Not to worry. Peppa.
I'm on my way.
[siren wailing]
[grown-ups coughing]
Hello, everyone.
Caught Pedro's cough, have we?
[all coughing]
Very well,
stand in line and open wide.
[all] Ew.
It tastes like custard and old socks.
[all laugh]
Thank you for looking after us,
Dr. Brown Bear.
Who looks after you when you're ill?
No one looks after me.
I'm never ill.
[coughing]
[narrator] Oh, dear.
Dr. Brown Bear has caught Pedro's cough.
Not to worry. [coughs]
Goodbye.
[all] Goodbye.
Poor Dr. Brown Bear.
He's ill and there's no one
to look after him.
[all] Oh.
[coughing]
[doorbell rings]
Who can that be?
Hello.
We've come to look after you.
[woofs] Here's some fruit.
[neighs] And some cushions.
And here is your medicine.
Ew.
It tastes like jammy yogurt-flavored
custard socks.
[children giggle]
And here's a song to make you feel better.
♪ Oh ♪
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is bedtime.
Good night, Peppa.
Good night, George.
[snorts] Can I have a story, please?
Okay.
I'll read you The Red Monkey book.
But we always have that one.
The Red Monkey has a bath,
cleans his teeth, and goes to sleep.
Uh... Yes, that is what happens.
Can we choose another story?
The Blue Tiger, The Green Spider,
The Orange Penguin.
Oh! What's this one?
The Wonderful World of Concrete.
I've been looking for that.
Is it your book, Daddy?
It's a book I borrowed from the library.
What's a library?
It's a place you borrow books from.
When you've finished reading them,
you take them back.
But Daddy Pig has forgotten
to take this book back.
I have had it for rather a long time.
Never mind.
You can take it back tomorrow. [snorts]
But now it's bedtime.
After Daddy reads this story.
It's not much of a story, Peppa.
Please read it, Daddy.
Okay.
[giggles]
The Wonderful World of Concrete.
"Concrete is a construction material
composed of sand, water
and chemical admixtures.
Chapter one, sand."
[Mommy Pig & children snoring]
[narrator] Peppa, George and Mommy Pig
have fallen asleep.
It is morning.
Peppa and her family have come
to the library.
[Peppa & George giggling]
-Wow! What a lot of books.
-Shh.
Peppa, you must be quiet in the library.
Why?
Because people come here to read
and to be quiet.
Next, please.
[narrator] Miss Rabbit is the librarian.
Hello, Mommy Pig.
Are you returning these books?
-Yes, Miss Rabbit.
-Right you are.
[computer beeping]
-Why is the computer beeping?
-It's checking to see
that you haven't been naughty
and borrowed the book for too long.
Um... I may have borrowed this book
for a bit too long.
Oh. Don't worry, Daddy Pig.
It can't be that bad.
[blaring]
Gosh, Daddy Pig, you've had this book out
for ten years.
Naughty, Daddy.
Sorry, Miss Rabbit.
That's all right.
Now you can borrow another book.
Miss Rabbit, can George and I
borrow a book, please?
Yes.
The children's section is over here.
[Peppa & George giggle]
Oh, look.
Fairies, flowers, pretty dresses.
[woofs] Hello, Peppa.
Oh, hello, Danny.
I'm borrowing a book about football.
[bleats] Hello, Peppa.
[snorts] Hello, Suzy.
-I've got a book about nurses.
-[George snorts]
[narrator] George has chosen a book
about dinosaurs.
Dine-saw. Grr.
[snorts] Look what I've found.
Further Adventures
in the World of Concrete.
Here's a Red Monkey book.
Not the Red Monkey book.
It's boring.
But this is a different story.
It might be more fun.
I bet it's not.
"Once upon a time,
there was a Red Monkey..."
Ugh. He had a bath, cleaned his teeth
and went to bed.
[Mommy Pig] No.
"He jumped in a space rocket
and went to the moon.
[children] Ooh.
[Mommy Pig] He had a picnic
with a dinosaur and swam under the sea
and climbed the highest mountain.
That was a busy day.
The end."
Wow! Read it again.
We can borrow it
and read it at home, Peppa.
But I was going to choose this book
or this one.
You can take three books home
if you want, Peppa.
Yippee!
But you must remember
to bring them back on time.
Yes, Miss Rabbit.
And you must remember
to bring your book back, too, Daddy Pig.
[giggles] I'll make sure Daddy remembers.
Yes, Peppa, I'm sure you will.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and George
are very excited today.
They are going on holiday.
Oh, where's Daddy?
[snorts] He's bringing a secret surprise.
[horn honking]
What's that?
[snorts] It's a camper van.
We've borrowed it for our holiday.
Ooh.
This camper van has everything.
This button works the sink.
[both] Wow.
And this button works the TV.
[both giggling]
What does this button do?
I'm not sure.
Maybe don't press it until we know.
[snorts] Is everybody ready
to go on holiday?
[Daddy Pig & children] Yes, Mommy Pig.
Then let's go.
[Peppa giggles]
♪ We're going on holiday
In a camper van ♪
[horn honks]
[all laugh]
Hmm. This map is a bit tricky.
Daddy, we don't want to get lost.
[Daddy Pig] Don't worry, Peppa.
I'm an expert at map reading.
Oh, that's strange.
-Are we lost?
-Uh...
Yes.
[narrator] It's Granddad Dog
with Danny Dog.
[woofs] Hello, Peppa.
Hello, Danny.
We're lost.
[woofs] Lost?
Is your satnav broken?
Satnav?
You're driving a camper van T3200.
Satnav comes as standard.
[computer] Welcome to the car
of the future.
Ah.
So, that's what that button does.
[computer] Where are we going today?
The camper van is talking.
Clever, isn't it?
The computer voice helps you
find your way.
But how does it know where we want to go?
You tell it.
Uh, hello, Mrs. Camper Van.
[computer] Hello.
We're going on holiday.
Can you tell us the way?
[computer] Proceed on the current road
in a straight line.
Thanks for your help, Granddad Dog.
You're welcome.
Have a lovely holiday.
♪ We're going on holiday
In a camper van ♪
[all laughing]
[alarm blaring]
[computer] Danger, danger.
Oil is low.
What's oil?
Oil helps engines to run smoothly.
Will the oil run out?
No.
These warnings always give you
plenty of time.
[computer] Oil is gone.
[engine clunks]
Oh, dear.
Luckily, I've got a spare can of oil.
Well done, Daddy Pig.
[snorts] We simply pour the oil
into the engine and--
-Oh.
-What's wrong?
There's nothing in here.
The engine's gone.
[horn honks]
[narrator] It's Mommy Sheep
with Suzy Sheep.
Hello, Suzy.
[bleats] Hello, Peppa.
We've lost our engine.
Lost your engine?
Yes. [snorts] It's completely disappeared.
I'd like to help,
but I don't know a thing about engines.
I'm probably just being silly,
but this looks a bit like an engine.
Oh, yes.
Well spotted, Mommy Sheep.
[narrator] The camper van has its engine
at the back.
There.
That should be enough oil.
Thank you, Mommy Sheep.
You're welcome.
Have a lovely holiday.
Are we nearly there yet?
[computer] Just up the next hill.
You have reached your destination.
[all] Hooray!
Time for bed.
[snorts] Where will we sleep?
Mommy Pig and I will sleep on this bed.
Ooh.
-And you two will sleep upstairs.
-But there isn't an upstairs.
Oh-ho. Watch this.
[narrator] The camper van's roof
is lifting up.
[Peppa] The camper van is just like
our little house. [giggles]
While we're on holiday,
it is our little house.
[Peppa & George giggle]
[Daddy Pig] Good night, my little piggies.
[Peppa] Good night.
-[child giggles]
-[Peppa snorts]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
-[child giggles]
[Peppa snorts]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
-[Peppa snorts]
-[children giggle]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
-[Peppa snorts]
-[children giggle]